Research and Dean of Graduate Studies, Office of the Vice President for; Records ua400
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Division for Research Records
1974-2013
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
ua400
42.88 cubic ft.
This collection contains records from the Office of the Vice President for Research and Dean of Graduate Studies, which oversaw research and graduate education at the University between 1971 and 1998.
Access
Researchers may access this collection, yet often files must be reviewed by an archivist to ensure compliance with New York State Public Records laws. Please consult an archivist for more information.
Acquisition Information
All items in this collection were transferred to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives.
Administrative History
The Office of the Vice President for Research and Dean of Graduate Studies was created in 1971 as a result of the combination of the Offices of Research and Graduate Studies. The Office's duties were two-fold: Firstly, the Dean of Graduate Studies was responsible for overseeing graduate education at the University, including program development, graduate student recruitment and retention, student travel grants and guidelines, academic grievances and the development of graduate programs with international universities. The Vice President of Research's portion of the Office was primarily dedicated to the promotion and facilitation of faculty research, with a focus on reviewing grant requests and overseeing the dispersal of institutional grants and other funding to faculty. Generally, a single person filled both roles. The Office also played a part in the development and financing of research centers and the dispersal of Faculty Research Awards. For a number of years, the role of Vice President of Research and Dean of Graduate Studies was filled by Jeanne Gullahorn, whose tenure of office makes up a large portion of this collection. In 1998, the Division for Research was created and the Vice President for Research was folded into that office, while the Division of Academic Affairs assumed responsibility for graduate education and international graduate programs.
Scope and Contents
The records in this collection were created by various individuals in the Office of the Vice President for Research and Dean of Graduate Studies. Materials include: Vice President search committee records; administrative files relating to other university departments; records of research centers and institutes, including: the Center for Women in Government, the Center for Computing and Disability, the Center for Legislative Development, the Center for Technology and Government, and others; records from various international programs; council and committee files, including: the Council on Research, Committee on Centers and Institutes, Graduate Academic Council, and others; faculty salary information and performance reviews; budget files and account expenditure summaries; files relating to the Research Foundation; files relating to the Office of Laboratory Animal Services; and various other records relating to the administration of graduate education and research.
A small portion of the collection dates from 1999-2002, after the Office of the Vice President for Research and Dean of Graduate Studies was dissolved. These materials are largely intermixed with the earlier records and represent the transition to the current Office for Research Includes subject administrative files relating to other university departments, records of research centers and institutes, council and committee files, faculty files, UUP records, correspondence, and Office for Research records.
Arrangement of the Collection
This collection has been broken up into 10 series. Most series have been arranged in the order in which they were transferred to the archives. As collections were not transferred chronologically, items within the collection are not in chronological order. The Articulation Agreements and International Programs series, the Search Committee series, and the Publications series have been created artificially from material found in several other series.
Education, Higher--Administration; Universities and colleges--Graduate work; Research; Administrative records; UAlbany Academic Administration; State University of New York at Albany
- Administrative Records, 1992 July 17 addition, 1974-1992; 9.57 cubic ft.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains correspondence sent to and from the Office of the Vice President for Research and Dean of Graduate Studies. This series contains documentation on both proposed and approved Research Centers and Institutes affiliated with the Univeristy. Contains polices regarding research misconduct, funding requests, office travel vouchers and nominations for the Faculty Research Awards Program.
  Arrangement
  Folders in this series were maintained in their original order upon processing.
  - President, 1980-1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Assistant to the President, 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - UP Academic Affairs, 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Vice Pres. For Student Affairs, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - VP Finance + Business Mgmt. Mr.Hartigan, 1982-1985 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - UP University Affairs Dr. L. Welch, 1982-1989 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Vice Chancellor for Intl. Programs, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Asst VP + Controller, 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Office of the Provost, 1982-1985 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Chancellor, 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Finance + Business, 1982-1985 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Research Foundation, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Research Foundation, 1986; 1987; 1988 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Graduate Education + Research, 1982-1985 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Graduate Admissions Office, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Research Office, 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - ASRC, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - ASRC, 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Cartography and Remote Sensing Lab, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Centers + Institutes Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Committee on Centers + Institutes, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Committee on Centers + Institutes, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Committee on Centers + Institutes, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Centers and Institutes, 1981-1982; 1984-1987 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Center for Applied Psychological Research, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Center for Behavioral Teratology, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Biotech, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Center for Brazilian + Portuguese Studies, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - SUNY Center for Comparative Literature Studies, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Center for Comparative Urban and Regional Research, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Center for Computing & Disability, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Center for Court and Legislative Studies, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Center for Disaster Management, 1982; 1984 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Center for Educational Research and Policy Studies, 1982-1985 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Center for Financial Management, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Center for Global Resources, 1982; 1987 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Center for Government Technology Solutions, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Center for Governmental Research and Services, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Center for Information Management, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Center for Info. Management, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Center for Latin America and the Caribbean, 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Ctr. for Mental Health Policy, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Center on Minorities + Criminal Justice, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Center for Organizational + Policy Studies, 1981; 1983 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Center for Research and Development, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Center for Research on Family/Group Decision Making, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Center for Research and Development, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Center for Research on Social Work Intervention, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Center for Social + Demographic Research, 1981-1982; 1984-1988 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Center for Stress + Anxiety Disorder, 1981-1982; 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Center for the Study of Public Management, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Center for Telecommunication, 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Center for Undergraduate Education, 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Comparative Development Studies Center, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Development Center for Business, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Financial Markets Research Center, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Management Assistance Center, 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Psychological Services Center, 1981; 1988 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Inst. for Decision Systems, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Institute of Gerontology, 1981-1982; 1985; 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - ISIS, 1985-1988 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Institute for Government and Policy Studies, 1981-1982; 1984; 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Institute for Human Services Policy Research, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Institute for Humanistic Studies, 1981; 1983 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Institute for Interdisciplinary Studies, Undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Institute for Research on Women, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - IRIS Newsletter Inst. for Renaissance Inter-disciplinary studies, 1982-1984; 1986 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Institute for Traffic Safety, 1982-1985 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Hindelang Criminal Justice Research Center, 1980-1985 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - New York State Writers Institute, 1983-1984; 1986 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Continuing Studies, 1982-1985 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Rockefeller College, 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Public Affairs Office of the Dean, 1981-1982; 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Information Science Office of the Dean, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Education Office of the Dean, 1982-1985 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Business Office of the Dean, 1981; 1983-1985 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Dean College of Humanities and Fine Arts, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Dean College of Science and Math, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Dean College of Social and Behavioral Sciences, 1981; 1983-1985 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Anthropology, 1983-1985 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Afro-American Studies, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Astronomy and Space Science, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Atmospheric Science, 1981-1984 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Biological Sciences, 1983-1985 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Chemistry, 1975; 1982; 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - History, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Philosophy, 1981-1984 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Physics, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Psychology, 1983-1985 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Sociology, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Professional Development Program, 1981-1989 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Space Astronomy Lab, 1975-1976; 1979-1981; 1983 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Albany/New Paltz/IBM, 1982-1983; 1985 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Budget, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Budget Meetings, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Capital Region Economic Development Consortium (CAPREDCON), 1981 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Budget OR5, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Community University Day, 1983-1984; 1986 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Cooperative Agreement between SUNY/A and Albany Medical college, 1980-1982 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Court Systems Management Program, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Dudley Observatory, 1976; 1984 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Experiencing Albany Past - Present - Future, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Faculty/Staff Development, 1982 January 4-1984 October 12 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Franco- American and Quebec Heritage Series, 1983-1985; 1987; 1989 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Global Education, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Graduate Assistantships/ Fellowships, 1983-1985 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - High Technology assistance Center, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Honors Convocation, 1982-1983; 1985 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Management Development, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Mid-Hudson Institute Of Management, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Neuroscience, 1987-1989 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - N.Y.S Research University ASSN., 1983 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - N.Y.S Science & Technology Found (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Office and Program Reorganization, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Organizational Studies? Ph.D., 1986-1988 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Research Misconduct Policies 1 of 6, 1983-1990 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Research Misconduct Policies 2 of 6, 1983-1990 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Research Misconduct Policies 3 of 6, 1983-1990 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Research Misconduct Policies 4 of 6, 1983-1990 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Research Misconduct Policies 5 of 6, 1983-1990 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Research Misconduct Policies 6 of 6, 1983-1990 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Parking, 1983-1987 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Peace Corps, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Personal Safety, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Personnel Administration, 1985-1989 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Program Registration and Review, 1984-1985; 1987-1988; 1990 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Promotions & Continuing Appointments Guidelines, 1985 August 30 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Health Policy, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Meeting re Research Assoc. Series Mon Aug 21 - 1:30 pm SUNY T.401, 1988 November 14-1989 August 24 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - RFP/Centers + Institutes, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Research University Consortium, 1983 May 12 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Residency Requirements, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - ROTC, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - SUNY - PRT, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - RPI - SUNY Industrial Collaboration, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - RPI Incubator Program - Symposium on Industrial Innovation: Industry - University- Government Interaction, 1982 October 12 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Albert Schweitzer Chair, 1983-1988 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Soviet Satellite System, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - State Education Department, 1985; 1987; 1989 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - (SIRS) Student Information Record Systems, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - SUNYA Foundation, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Teacher Education & the Disciplines, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Telephone and Tie Line Service, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Title III, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Title III Designation Request, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Sample grant for Strengthening Institutions Dept. of Education Program, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Title 3, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - TV Channel 10, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - UAC and GAC Joint Reviews, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - University Budget Panel, 1980; 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - University Bus Services (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - University Center for Organizational Effectiveness, 1987-1990 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - University Excellence Awards, 1984; 1986 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Use of University Facilities by Non - Commercial Organizations, 1978; 1981; 1983-1985 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - WAMC (Albany Medical College), 1981; 1983 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - World Cultures Week, 1983-1984; 1986-1988 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Academic Policy Groups minutes + Correspondence, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Academic Policy Groups minutes (1 of 5), 1988 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Academic Policy Groups minutes (2 of 5), 1988 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Academic Policy Groups minutes (3 of 5), 1988 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Academic Policy Groups minutes (4 of 5), 1988 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Academic Policy Groups minutes (5 of 5), 1988 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Academic Policy Groups, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Council on Research, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Council on Research, 1986-1988 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Presidents Management Committee - Vice Presidents' Meetings, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Vice Presidents' Meetings, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Council of Deans, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Council of Deans, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Council on Ed. Policy, 1987-1989 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Administrative Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - SUNY Doctoral Council Cost Recovery Advisory Group, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Industrial Linkages, 1981-1983; 1987 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Racial Concerns across the Campus, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Computer Allocations Committee, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Council of Women's Groups, 1986; 1988 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Council for International Exchange of Scholars, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - EPD, 1986-1988 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Minority Undergrad. Recruitment Subcomm Undergraduate Recruitment Subcommittee Undergraduate Retention Subcommittee, 1983-1985 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Private Funding Coordination Committee, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Professional Development Committee, 1984 November 19-1985 December 26 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Resource Management Group, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - University Computing Advisory Committee, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - University Policy Conference, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Council on Deans, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - University Senate Minutes, 1987-1990 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Travel vouchers, 1990 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Travel vouchers, 1989 July 1-1990 June 30; 1988 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - RF - Travel + Purchase Requisitions, 1989 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - RF - Travel + Purchase Requisitions, 1988 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Council on Research, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Council on Research, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Council on Res, 1986-1988 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Council on Research, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Council on Research, 1987-1989 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Council on Research, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Council on Research, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Council on Research, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Committee on Centers and Institutes, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Centers and Institutes, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Conferences on Campus, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Journals + Conferences, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Journals and Conferences Committee, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Journal and Conferences, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Journal and Conferences, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Research Incentives Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Research Incentives Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Research Incentives Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Excellence in Research, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Prof. Kajal Lahiri Excellence in Research 1988 Nomination (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Excellence in Research Nomination Material for J. Fetterly, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Distinguished Service Professorship, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Distinguished Service Professor, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Distinguished Service Professorship, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Res & Grad Studies Diversity Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - New Faculty Luncheons, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - New Faculty Reception, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - New Faculty Receptions, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Center Development 1988-1989 Racial/Ethnic Res. (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Meetings with Center Directors, 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Meetings with Center Directors, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Campus Statistics Group Formulation & Meetings, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Statistics Program, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Material, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - State Committee Meeting, 1988 April 14 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Syllabi & Course Info Summary, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Syllabi - Statistics Courses - J. Gullahorn request, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Research Faculty Exchange GRI Funded, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Publication for Laurie Kozakiewicz, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Exchanges GRI Program, 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Research Mentor Program, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - RFP Seed Funding Centers and Institutes, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Committee Meetings / University Committee Applied Science, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - External Advisory Committee, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Private Sector Initiatives, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Targeted faculty / F.U. and Reports, 1986-1988 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Targeted Researchers, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Center and Institute Review, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Faculty Research Awards Program Competition, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Faculty Research Awards Program Notification Letters, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Faculty Research Awards Program Competition, 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - FRAP Questionnaires, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Five Year Plan Update, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Five Year Plan, 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Five Year Plan Update, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Quincentenary, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Task Force Questionnaires Ind. EO Bus / EO Linkages, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - University Committee on Applied Science Meetings, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - NIH Biomedical Research Support Grant, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - NIH Biomedical Research Support Grant, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Professional Women's Luncheon Series, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - United Way/ SEFA, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Campus Shutdown Intercession, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Unite Way Campaign, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Career Expo - Albany, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - New Faculty Meetings, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - New Faculty Receptions, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - GRI Postdoctoral Positions, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - PDS Committee (Personnel Data System), 1989 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Research Set up for New Minority Faculty, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Divisional Diversity Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Organizational Studies Research Project on Graduate Admissions Office, 1990 April 1-1990 July 4 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Search Committee Project Staff Associate, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - UUP Contract, 1988-1991 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - NYS/UUP Cultural Diversity Program, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - NYS/UUP New Faculty Development Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - New Faculty Development Awards, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - NYS/ UUP Experienced Faculty Travel Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - New Faculty Development Awards, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - NYS/UUP Recommendations, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence NYS/UUP, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Exp. Faculty Travel, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Experience Faculty Travel Awards, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Experience Faculty Travel Awards, 1989-1990; 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - NYS/UUP Excellence Awards, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Professional Leaves, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - NYS/UUP Applications, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Professional Study Leave Awards Program, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Librarian Leaves, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Librarian Study Leaves, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Professional & Librarian Leaves PDQWL, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - PDQWL Correspondence [1 of 2], 1989 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - PDQWL Correspondence [2 of 2], 1987 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - PDQWL Committee Guidelines + Award Recipients, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - PDQWL Award Programs General Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - PDQWL General Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - PDQWL General Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Nuala McGann Drescher Program, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Nuala McGann Drescher, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Nuala McGann Drescher Affirmative Action Leave Program, 1989 September 1 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Nuala McGann Drescher Affirmative Action Leave Program, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - NYS/UUP - New Faculty Background, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 1)